questrade.com 2007-02-27

# 

                                                                                                                          P R I VA C Y
                                                                                                                          POLICY
 PRIVACY POLICY
  The Questrade, Inc. ("Questrade") privacy policy applies to all current or former Questrade brokerage Clients or who regis-
  ter for one of our services or promotional offers. Throughout the policy, we refer to information that personally identifies
  you or your Accounts as "personal information."
  1. We do not sell your personal information to anyone.
  2. The law allows you to "opt out" of only certain kinds of information sharing with third parties. Questrade does not share per-
  sonal information about you with any third parties that triggers this opt out right. This means YOU ARE ALREADY OPTED OUT.
  Questrade only shares personal information with third parties in the following limited circumstances:
        •   We disclose personal information to companies that help us process or service your transactions or Account(s),
            including companies that clear and process your transactions and print and mail your Account statements.
        •   Sometimes we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing your Account. Our con-
            tracts with such third parties prohibits them from using any of your personal information for their own purposes, and
            the third parties are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we have provided to them.
        •   We may also enter into what is called a "joint marketing relationship" with another financial institution, if we believe that
            you might be interested in hearing about its products or services. If we enter into such a relationship, we have contracts
            in place to ensure that the other financial institution will protect the confidentiality of the limited information we would
            share with it (e.g., name and address), and that it will use your personal information only for the joint marketing arrangement.
        •   We may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure
            is required or permitted under law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate
            with regulators or law enforcement authorities, resolve Client disputes, perform credit/authentication checks,
            or for institutional risk control.
        •   For regulatory purposes, self regulatory organizations including Market Regulation Services Inc., the Investment
            Dealers Association of Canada, and the Canadian Investor Protection Fund (collectively, "SROs") require access to
            personal information of current and former Clients, employees, agents, directors, officers, partners and others that
            has been collected or used by Regulated Persons. SROs collect, use or disclose such personal information obtained
            from Regulated Persons for regulatory purposes, including:
        •   Surveillance of trading-related activity, sales, financial compliance, trade desk review and other regulatory audits,
        •   Investigation of potential regulatory and statutory violations,
        •   Regulatory databases,
        •   Enforcement or disciplinary proceedings,
        •   Reporting to Securities regulators, and
        •   Information-sharing with Securities regulatory authorities, regulated marketplaces, other self-regulatory organizations
            and law enforcement agencies in any jurisdiction in connection with any of the foregoing.
  3. We collect personal information in the normal course of business in order to administer your Accounts and serve you better.
        •   Application and registration information. We collect information that you provide to us when you open an Account
            or register for one of our services, or when you accept a promotional offer for a Questrade-sponsored product or
            ser vice. The information we collect may include name, address, phone number, email address, social insurance
            numb er, and informat ion ab out your invest ment s, and invest ment ex p er i ence. We also may c olle c t informa-
            tion from consumer reporting agencies to verify your identity in the Account opening process.
        •   Web Site usage. We collect some information from our web sites through the use of "cookies." For example we may
            identify the pages on our web sites that your browser request s or visit s. This information is only p ersonally
            identifiable if you have chosen to identify yourself, for example, by opening an Account.
Last Modified: August 4, 2006                                                                                                         1 of 2

                                                                                                               P R I VA C Y
                                                                                                               POLICY
      •   Transaction information. Once you have an Account with us, to administer your Account and serve you better, we
          collect and maintain personal information about your transactions, including balances, positions, and account his-
          tory, and may include your name or other data in an internal Client list that reflects your activities at Questrade.
      •   As part of our efforts to reach and serve new and existing Clients we sometimes collect and use information from
          outside mailing lists.
4. We use your personal information to help us deliver the best possible service to you.
      •   To understand your financial needs and to deliver financial products and services that meet them, we may share
          personal information, such as transaction or experience data, with various service providers, all of which follow
          similar privacy policies.
5. We protect the confidentiality and Security of your personal information.
      •   Companies we hire to provide support ser vices are not allowed to use your personal information for their own
          purposes and are contractually obligated to maintain strict confidentiality. We limit their use of your personal
          information to the performance of the specific service we have requested.
      •   We restrict access to personal information to our employees and agents for business purposes only. All employees
          are trained and required to safeguard such information.
      •   We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information.
6. We continue to evaluate our effort s to protect personal information and make ever y effort to keep your personal
information accurate and up to date.
      •   If you identify any inaccuracy in your personal information, or you need to make a change to that information,
          please contact us so that we may promptly update our records.
7. We will provide notice of changes in our information-sharing practices. If, at any time in the future, it is necessary to dis-
close any of your personal information in a way that is inconsistent with this policy, we will give you advance notice of the pro-
posed change so that you will have the opportunity to opt-out of such disclosure.
COOKIES
"Cookies" are small amounts of data that a web site can send to your browser and store on your computer. Cookies do not
contain personal information about you (unless you knowingly provide it). Cookies can note that your browser was used to
visit certain sites, pages, or advertisements on a certain date. Questrade uses cookies to enhance navigation and function-
ality of our web site, to securely verify your identity, and to personalize aspects of your experience on our web site.
Questrade also uses cookies to let us know how visitors are using the Questrade web site, so that we can improve our web
site and your experience on it. Questrade also uses the information collected from cookies to ensure that prospective Clients
receive incentive offers for which they have qualified.
Questrade may permit certain third party ad servers to set cookies through the Questrade website to track performance of
advertisements and to collect aggregate data on web page viewing. You do have control over cookies. Most browsers can be
set to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. You can set most browsers to refuse to accept cookies,
although this may affect your Internet experience. You can also erase cookies that are already on your computer.
For more information on working with cookies, you should consult the User Manual, FAQ , or Help function of your specific
browser and operating system software.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES
Our web site contains links to other web sites. Questrade is not responsible for the privacy policy and privacy practices of
any other web sites.
Last Modified: August 4, 2006                                                                                                2 of 2
